oifc.in 2010-04-29

# OIFC : Privacy Policy

|   
---  
---  
|  |   
---|---  
|  |  |   
---|---|---  
|  | Privacy Policy  
---  
| OIFC is committed to maintaining the trust and confidence of visitors to our web site. We will not sell, rent or trade your personal information under any circumstances.  
---  
  
  * We may track domain names, IP addresses, and browser types from people who visit our site. 
    * We use this information to track aggregate traffic patterns throughout the OIFC site. We will not correlate this information with any personal information. 

  * In cases where we do retain information about visitors to our site and the E-mail addresses of people who write to us, this information is stored in our off-line secure computing environment, not on the web. 
    * We store this information, but we do not sell it or release it to third parties. 

  * We do not use cookies to track information about a user's movements throughout our site. 
    * However, when making a purchase, users will be redirected to our payment processing service that may use and/or require the use of cookies for placing an order online. 

  * We may need to pass on user feedback to our knowledge partners. When doing so we may need to pass on user email IDs. Our knowledge partners will also be bound by the OIFC privacy policy. 

If you have any questions or comments about this policy, our services, or your experience with our site you can contact us by email at [privacy@oifc.in](mailto:privacy@oifc.in) (suggestive)  
---
